Okay,
that's it
for today's class.
Everyone, go prepare well.
Okay?
Okay.
Senior Gu Chenyang.
Chen Song.
Interstellar Slam Dunk: Heart of the Machine.
This is my new script.
You're the second reader.
The first one is Li Haoyu.
Yeah.
He said I could
show it to you.
What's this?
A sci-fi movie?
Not only a sci-fi movie,
but also a sports drama.
It's about a team of
abandoned robots
in the future.
The inspiration for this story
comes from our Basketball Club.
I even added
a role of a captain,
whose code name is Dubhe.
He is the brain of the team,
with a cool personality
and meticulous planning.
No matter how perilous the situation,
as long as he is there,
it will be turned into safety
and lead to victory.
Senior Gu Chenyang,
this character
is based on you.
At the last Arts Festival,
your quick thinking backstage
was just so cool.
I heard the basketball team
lost two games recently,
but I believe
as long as you're there,
you will definitely turn the tide.
Really?
Of course.
Thank you.
But I've only thought about
the character setting and details.
I haven't thought about how to write the script.
Please give me some advice
after you read it.
Okay.
I'll go now, senior.
Coach
I...
I can still dribble with my left hand.
I can play today.
What tactic?
Come here.
Sit down.
You sitting down is the tactic.
Coach
I saw the tactic
you sent yesterday.
It's a little bit complicated.
What's complicated?
I can explain it in detail.
It's not your fault.
We don't have enough time.
There's only a week left before the game.
Changing tactics at the last minute is a big no-no.
But I...
I know you're anxious.
But sometimes,
it's better to do nothing than to do something wrong.
Listen.
Come on.
Check the notes for today.
Li Haoyu.
Li Haoyu can't control the ball.
He's like playing with it every day.
Yes.
Chenyang is right.
And Lin Qingyuan.
Lin Qingyuan tends to lose focus on the field.
He missed several balls yesterday.
Yeah.
Well,
I think so.
Zhou Yang.
Zhou Yang needs
to be more active.
Only in this way
can he link us up.
Okay.
Bin Yan.
I know.
How long have you slept
since yesterday?
Just a heads-up,
the tactics you sent
in the group at 3 AM.
I know you have
many reasons for turning me down.
But your tense state
might affect everyone.
You should go rest first.
It's better for everyone.
Did you convince him?
Isn't it obvious?
That's good.
Gu Chenyang,
go back to training.
Training what?
How can I train when you're like this?
What's going on with you?
I just don't have confidence.
The pressure is huge.
Will a plan give you confidence?
Plans can't keep up with changes.
Alright.
I have
a very important plan.
I must take you to carry it out.
What plan?
Super Invincible Lazy Fish Plan.
Don't be so stiff.
There's no surveillance here.
Do you want to settle the matter
like we did when we were kids?
No need.
I'm not in the mood.
Mood is something
that comes with playing.
The way you are now
is so similar to that day.
Which day?
The day we broke up.
You're amazing.
For the school charity,
each class
has the teacher arrange the activity.
But you applied for
the charity sale.
I heard everyone praising you.
Actually, it was my dad
who suggested it to me.
He said I'm already ten years old
and should try to independently plan
and execute an event.
Only in the process of practice
can I grow up better.
Is it necessary?
The purpose of the school
is to
convey love happily.
Look.
The Hand-holding Cat is finished.
Isn't it cute?
So cute.
This will be a hit
at tomorrow's sale.
Right.
My dad said we must
check everything
one more time
before the sale.
I gotta go.
What...
What's the rush?
What could go wrong?
As long as the dolls are cute,
they'll sell well,
and the event will be a success.
Look how cute this doll is.
This is the soul of the fundraiser.
That makes sense.
Let's work harder
and make more.
Let's put on the clothes first.
Okay.
Hello, Mr. Li.
Why haven't the students come?
Wasn't the event canceled?
It wasn't canceled.
But the venue is leaking.
We've moved to a new place.
We all thought it was canceled.
Didn't you notify everyone?
No,
I didn't.
Can the students still come?
It's too late today.
They won't make it in time.
Alright then.
Aunt Zhang,
it's me,
Yang.
I've been looking for a while,
but I still can't find
your place.
I'm on a small path
next to the original venue.
Never mind.
I need to go grocery shopping.
Maybe next time.
You're leaving?
Alright then.
Hello, Aunt Sun.
Hello, Uncle Li.
Hello, Uncle Zhao.
Hello, Uncle Wang.
We've changed the venue.
Can you still come?
It's okay.
Gu Chenyang,
I'm back.
Look at these.
Are they enough?
This...
Only one was sold this afternoon.
It's okay.
I'll shout.
Charity sale!
Show your love for the children in the mountains!
Stop shouting.
It's over.
Well,
I'll buy them all.
I brought my lucky money.
Don't be like this.
It's not your fault
that the venue had a problem.
It's my fault.
My dad told me
to confirm all the details in advance
to ensure everything goes smoothly.
I didn't listen to him
and carry it out properly.
So you're blaming me?
Yesterday,
I was the one who dragged you away
and didn't let you confirm everything.
That's not what I meant.
I'll just buy this box, and that's it.
Can you just leave me alone?
This is my charity event.
I don't need you to meddle.
I gave up surfing
just to spend time with you.
I didn't ask you to.
Fine.
I was just bored.
I picked up this cat
the next day.
I waited at your house
all night, but you never came back.
Then you just disappeared
for the whole summer.
When you came back,
you were like a different person.
I'm sorry.
Actually, that day,
I wasn't blaming you.
I was blaming myself.
My dad was right.
Losing control comes with a price.
Students,
teachers,
parents,
so many people believed in me
and were looking forward to that event.
But I messed it up.
That feeling,
I really don't want
to go through it again.
Gu Chenyang,
I bring this up again
isn't to hear your apology.
I just don't like the way you are now.
You're always
pushing yourself too hard.
You pretend you're not tired,
but I can see it.
So,
you don't like the way I am now?
Not exactly.
Both the old you
and the new you
are both pretty cool.
But the point is what do you think?
You are not just your dad's son.
You are also yourself.
So you
are not mad at me anymore?
It was not me who broke up with you.
I'm not
that narrow-minded, okay?
Now I have one thing
that is not in my plan,
but
it's a high priority.
What?
I'm hungry.
You cut it...
Can you cut it properly?
You'd better
take care of your own hand.
Don't get the vegetable leaves on your face.
At your efficiency,
if I don't help,
you might faint from hunger before dinner's ready.
It must be Zhou Yang and the others arriving.
I'll go check.
Okay.
Dad,
weren't you coming back the day after tomorrow?
I finished my business early.
What's with this outfit?
You've really come into your own while I was away.
Cooking for yourself,
Some friends from the team
are coming over for hot pot.
Really?
Your soccer team
has at least ten people, right?
Dad,
it's a basketball team,
just five people.
Well,
are there any girls?
No.
Aunt Su and I don't have time to cook.
Just order some food.
Don't hurt yourself.
Thank you, Dad.
Awesome.
Come on.
Put the beef in the fridge.
Later,
for Xiaoyu and his friends.
Have fun with your friends.
Thank you, Aunt Su.
Don't go up there.
The kitchen is my turf now.
Don't go there.
Who wants to go?
Don't touch that yogurt.
There's mango in it.
You actually remember I don't eat mango.
Yu.
We're here.
Why is your door open?
I'm waiting for you.
Let's go.
Help me.
Drag it.
Don't you change your shoes?
No need.
Let's go.
Don't steal my meat.
This is mine.
Why do you take it?
Come on.
Thanks.
By the way,
why didn't Xu Anbo come today?
He can't leave the boxing gym.
He said
it's a competition for the elementary school students.
That's what he said last time.
And the time before last.
Is there a competition
every day in his gym?
Fu Binyan is even worse.
He doesn't even reply to messages.
He did reply.
What does the ellipsis mean?
It means "I have read it".
I'll take my leave.
It's still nice to be with us.
We're always here for you.
That's right.
Come on.
Let's have a drink.
Okay.
Cheers.
Help yourself.
Dig in.
There's plenty more.
Let's have some more.
You know what?
Back when basketball was invented,
they used to shoot into
bottomed baskets like this.
Perfect!
How about we use this basket
for a shooting contest?
Two people per team.
The loser
scrubs the pot, how about that?
Agreed.
Lin Qingyuan,
Zhou Yang,
do you two want to consider
snatching me?
Now Gu Chenyang's hand is injured.
He only has his left hand.
His body is unsteady.
Maybe he can't shoot
as well as I can.
You can try.
Fine.
Lin Qingyuan,
who do you pick?
I pick
Gu Chenyang.
Because I think
his left hand
is steadier than your right hand.
I also pick Gu Chenyang.
Fine.
You guys really have no taste.
Later, I'll let you
see the true power
of Yibei's sharpshooter.
Give me the hoop.
Really?
Let's see what you've got.
You're the real deal.
That doesn't count.
There's water.
My hand slipped.
Do it again.
Truly a skilled archer.
Alright, alright.
Let's have hot pot.
Who's texting this late?
This weekend, the Leo meteor shower
reaches its peak.
If you miss it, you'll have to wait another year.
This weekend's training mission:
have fun,
and enjoy yourselves.
I'll cover all expenses.
But,
you guys,
don't try to take advantage of me.
Then tonight,
I'll make a stargazing guide.
Just take a break, One-Armed Warrior.
How about
we switch it up and let someone else plan?
Good idea.
Me.
I'll do it.
I'm best at having fun.
Alright.
I vote for Lin Qingyuan.
Me too.
I...
You don't matter anymore.
Thanks for the trust, everyone.
This weekend,
just watch me.
We'll look forward to it.
Come on.
One more.
Okay.
Come on.
Cheers.
Help yourself.
There's plenty.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
My pleasure.
Dig in.
Planning a trip?
Can I not be disturbed?
Sure.
Yuan is all grown up.
Planning trips on her own now.
Raising a child requires letting go.
Look,
when the time comes, they naturally grow up.
Speaking of which,
the last time we watched the meteor shower
was when we were
studying abroad together, right?
I was pregnant with Yuan at that time.
Shall we have another
romantic night under the meteor shower?
Sure.
Let's go.
Done.
Look,
my plan.
Not bad.
Nice, Lin Qingyuan.
Looks great.
What do you think?
Impressive, right?
Not bad.
Let's see the next page.
That's all.
That's all?
Just this one page?
I drew all night.
Give it to me.
Take it.
Go and enjoy it slowly.
Really, that's all?
The 11 o'clock island activity.
The important thing
is the activities on the island.
What to eat, play, and see?
You haven't planned any of this?
If I planned it all, where's the fun?
We'll explore the island as we go.
That's the real adventure.
Give it to me.
No wonder Chi Jia didn't want to come.
She must have guessed
what would happen.
Chen Xiaosong,
how did you get here?
Senior Gu Chenyang
and Senior Li Haoyu
invited me.
I was writing a story
about the Basketball Club.
I hope it doesn't turn into
a survival story.
How could that happen?
You have to believe me.
What's wrong?
One kilometer ahead,
on the southbound section of Binhai Avenue,
there was a multi-vehicle pile-up.
Traffic control is currently in effect.
Please wait patiently.
This traffic jam is as bad as a hot pot.
It's already 8:30.
It will take us
another 40 minutes.
We're gonna miss
the boat to Pingguang Island.
What do we do now?
From the moment
you laid out this plan,
I knew
today was gonna be a disaster.
I had a feeling this would happen,
so I made a backup plan.
Since we can't go to Pingguang Island,
the best choice now
is Baisha Island.
Baisha Island?
Yes.
Baisha Island
is only the fourth most popular,
not as popular as Pingguang Island,
but it also has a great
meteor observation spot,
and it's not crowded,
so it's very comfortable to visit.
You're the best.
You're professional.
Can we catch the boat
to Baisha Island?
Yes.
The boat leaves at 9:30.
There are still many tickets.
I'll buy them now.
Don't move.
I'll buy them.
You don't have to.
I said I'll buy it.
Give me a chance
to make amends.
Are you sure
this is the fourth most popular island,
not the fourth least?
Feels like there's nobody here.
It's so popular,
yet there's not even a tourist center.
Oh no,
it's really like survival on a deserted island.
I want to go home.
Me too.
Oh, no.
This is not Baisha Island.
No way.
I bought the ticket to Baisha Island.
How could it be?
Come and see.
Look.
This is Baisha Island.
It's pronounced differently.
We're going to Baisha Island.
Baisha means white sand.
Oh, no.
I didn't see it clearly.
There's no boat back.
I'm sorry.
I got you into this.
Where are you going, Fu Binyan?
We have no choice.
Let's find a place to stay.
We can't stay here until tomorrow.
You're right.
Since we're here,
let's take a stroll around.
Maybe there's more fun
in the hidden map.
Well said.
Let's go.
Go.